viabox.com 2017-06-06

# Viabox: #1 Leader in Package Forwarding | Free USA Address

At Viabox we are dedicated to safeguarding and preserving your privacy when visiting our site or communicating electronically with us.   
This Privacy Policy, together with our terms of use, provides an explanation as to what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you.  
We do update this Policy from time to time so please do review this Policy regularly.

**Information We Collect**

In operating our website we may collect and process the following data about you:

  * Details of your visits to our website and the resources that you access, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data.
  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our website, such as when you registered for information or make a purchase. 
  * formation provided to us when you communicate with us for any reason.

**Use of Cookies**

On occasion, we may gather information about your computer for our services and to provide statistical information regarding the use of our website to our advertisers.   
Such information will not identify you personally it is statistical data about our visitors and their use of our site. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever.  
Similarly to the above, we may gather information about your general internet use by using a cookie file. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically. This cookie file is stored on the hard drive of your computer as cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our website and the service that we provide to you.   
All computers have the ability to decline cookies. This can be done by activating the setting on your browser which enables you to decline the cookies. Please note that should you choose to decline cookies, you may be unable to access particular parts of our website.  
Our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control. Such cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on advertisements on our website.

**Use of Your Information**

The information that we collect and store relating to you is primarily used to enable us to provide our services to you. In addition, we may use the information for the following purposes:

  * To provide you with information requested from us, relating to our products or services. 
  * To provide information on other products which we feel may be of interest to you, where you have consented to receive such information.
  * To meet our contractual commitments to you.
  * To notify you about any changes to our website, such as improvements or service/product changes, that may affect our service.

If you are an existing customer, we may contact you with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you.  
Further, we may use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, so that you can be provided with information about unrelated goods and services which we consider may be of interest to you. We or they may contact you about these goods and services by any of the methods that you consented at the time your information was collected.  
Please be advised that we do not reveal information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers but we may, on occasion, provide them with aggregate statistical information about our visitors.

**Storing Your Personal Data**

Data that is provided to us is stored on our secure servers. Details relating to any transactions entered into on our site will be encrypted to ensure its safety.  
The transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and therefore we cannot guarantee the security of data sent to us electronically and transmission of such data is therefore entirely at your own risk. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password so that you can access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.

**Disclosing Your Information**

Where applicable, we may disclose your personal information to third parties:  

  * Where we are legally required by law to disclose your information.
  * To assist in fraud protection or investigation.

**Third Party Links**

You may find links to third party websites on our website. These websites should have their own privacy policies which you should check. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies whatsoever as we have no control over them.

As you would expect of us, we will take all reasonable measures to ensure that the personal information you provide through our website is held and managed securely. However, there is not a lot that you can do to help keep your personal information safe – not just on our website, but whenever you provide information online.  
Here are some simple ways you can improve the security of your information:

  * Use a secure browser
  * Encryption is the process through which sensitive information is scrambled before it is transmitted so that it remains private even if it is intercepted. 128-bit versions support it.
  * Security upgrades for some older browser versions are available. We recommend that you contact your preferred browser provider for further information.

Viabox.com is fully PCI Compliant and runs on a full secure https platform.  
Viabox also use enterprise strength security devices to protect your information.
